

JOSEPH MARI CASAS

Address: Dumlog Talisay City Cebu 6045

Phone: +63 920 604 0549

Email: casasjosephm@gmail.com

Website: kingevariste.github.io/myportfolio

SUMMARY

Native-like fluency in English whether in speaking or in writing. Experienced in high-workload environments. Has the ability to work under pressure. Punctual, Responsible and Hard-working. Background in Mathematics and Computer Science shows a passion for critical thinking and problem solving

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chat Support, Yubo

Nov 2021 - April 2022

- Moderated their discord server with over 1000 users
- · Managed tickets through their ticket system settling disputes and issues
- Hosted various events to increase engagement and relevancy in the NFT space.

Online Content Moderator, Alorica

Feb 2021 - Dec 2022

- Reviewed and filtered unwanted content such as but not limited to indecent imagery, copyrighted digital media and content that incites violence.
- Reviewed over 10k content per week
- · Accuracy of over 99%

Shoutcaster / Commentator, CESAFI

Jun 2023 - August 2024

- Commentated Official Tournaments in ENGLISH
- Backed by many sponsors including but not limited to Virginia Foods Inc. and PC Express.
- Aside from CESAFI, I have been hired to do commentating for Official City Hall and Big Brand
 Tournaments such as but not limited to Mandaue City Hall's Charter Day Tournament and Juicy
 Lemon's Juicy Legends Tournament.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Mathematics and Computer Science

July 2019 - Dec 2024

Cebu Institute of Technology - University

- Excelled in Abstract Mathematics
- Proficient in Peer-to-Peer Communication

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- **Technical Skills:** Microsoft Office, Google Sheets, Microsoft Visual Studio, Full Stack Developer.
- Languages: English, Filipino, Visayan, German.
- Awards/Activities: First Place in University of San Jose Recoletos Mathematician of the Year 2018